[{"answer": " Whats wrong Amy", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Oh, nothing", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 15, "question": " Whats wrong Amy", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " Come on.  I can tell something is bothering you.  Whats the matter", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Oh, nothing", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Well, Im just feeling like I chose the wrong major.  Im not sure if Engineering i", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Come on.  I can tell something is bothering you.  Whats the matter", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Why did you pick Engineering as your major", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Well, Im just feeling like I chose the wrong major.  Im not sure if Engineering i", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " My dad is an engineer and my parents have always wanted me to follow in hi", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Why did you pick Engineering as your major", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Is there something else youd rather study", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 26, "question": " My dad is an engineer and my parents have always wanted me to follow in hi", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Im not sure.  I kind of like music and working with children, but Im just s", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Is there something else youd rather study", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": "Maybe I can help.  I read an article online today called Five Signs You Shoul", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Im not sure.  I kind of like music and working with children, but Im just s", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " I guess so.  Why not", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Maybe I can help.  I read an article online today called Five Signs You Shoul", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": "OK.  Ill read five statements to you and you have to tell me if theyre true o", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 39, "question": " I guess so.  Why not", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 43, "question": "OK.  Ill read five statements to you and you have to tell me if theyre true o", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": "All right.  Heres the first one  youre bored to tears in your current majo", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 44, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " True.  My Engineering classes are so boring.  I try not to fall asleep in all of them", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 46, "question": "All right.  Heres the first one  youre bored to tears in your current majo", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " OK.  Heres number two  youre not making good grades in your majo", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 47, "question": " True.  My Engineering classes are so boring.  I try not to fall asleep in all of them", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " That one's true.  Im getting a D in Physics this term and a C in Engineering 203", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 53, "question": " OK.  Heres number two  youre not making good grades in your majo", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " OK, thats two trues.  Heres the third statement  you chose your curren", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 57, "question": " That one's true.  Im getting a D in Physics this term and a C in Engineering 203", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Ummm, true again, I guess.  My family always told me I was going to be a", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 61, "question": " OK, thats two trues.  Heres the third statement  you chose your curren", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " OK, lets look at the last two statements.  You keep reading or asking abou", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Ummm, true again, I guess.  My family always told me I was going to be a", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " True.  This last week I met with the career counselor on campus to talk abou", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 70, "question": " OK, lets look at the last two statements.  You keep reading or asking abou", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Another true.  I think this is telling us something.  So heres the last statemen", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 75, "question": " True.  This last week I met with the career counselor on campus to talk abou", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Thats true too.  All I keep thinking about is my major and whether I made th", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 79, "question": " Another true.  I think this is telling us something.  So heres the last statemen", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Im sorry.  It sounds like you really are preoccupied with this", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Thats true too.  All I keep thinking about is my major and whether I made th", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Yes, I am", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Im sorry.  It sounds like you really are preoccupied with this", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Well, all five statements of the quiz were true for you.  According to the article", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 88, "question": " Yes, I am", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " She said it was up to me to decide whats best for my future.  She couldnt decid", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Well, all five statements of the quiz were true for you.  According to the article", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": " Will being an engineer make you happy", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 97, "question": " She said it was up to me to decide whats best for my future.  She couldnt decid", "qSentId": 96},{"answer": " I dont think so.  I think I just need to do it  just change my major", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 98, "question": " Will being an engineer make you happy", "qSentId": 97},{"answer": " Ive changed mine twice since I started college  theres nothing wrong wit", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 99, "question": " I dont think so.  I think I just need to do it  just change my major", "qSentId": 98},{"answer": " I guess youre right.  Ill just need to break the news to my parents", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 103, "question": " Ive changed mine twice since I started college  theres nothing wrong wit", "qSentId": 102},{"answer": " Im sure theyll understand", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 104, "question": " I guess youre right.  Ill just need to break the news to my parents", "qSentId": 103},{"answer": " I hope so", "docId": "04-05", "aSentId": 105, "question": " Im sure theyll understand", "qSentId": 104}]
